{"data":[{"question":"The group of students had all thought the train ___ by the time they arrived.","a":"would have left","b":"was leaving","c":"would be leaving","d":"left","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Would have pp: used when talking about something that did not happen, or a situation that cannot exist ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"My pen ___ \"Neither will mine.\"","a":"is not writing","b":"won't be written","c":"won't write","d":"doesn't write","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"___ down the TV; our baby is asleep.","a":"Turn","b":"Turning","c":"To turn","d":"Turned","answer":"1","explain":"\n- An imperative sentence typically begins with the base form of a verb: Do it; Look at me...\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Where ___ my new high heels?","a":"has","b":"have","c":"are","d":"is","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express sth in general","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Lisa got an A in Chemistry. I ___ that she is very intelligent.","a":"will have heard","b":"am hearing","c":"was heard","d":"hear","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense:indicate the speaker believes that a fact was true before, is true now, and will be true in the future. It is not important if the speaker is correct about the fact. It is also used to make generalizations about people or things","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Nelson is so rich that he ___ work.","a":"hasn't to","b":"hasn't been","c":"didn't have to","d":"doesn't have to","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense:indicate the speaker believes that a fact was true before, is true now, and will be true in the future. It is not important if the speaker is correct about the fact. It is also used to make generalizations about people or things ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"I won't go home until the job ___.","a":"had been done","b":"has been done","c":"is done","d":"will be done","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"When Ms. Hu arrived, the Pengs _________ supper.","a":"have already had","b":"was having","c":"had","d":"had already had","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. \n+ Past Perfect, when simple past tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"After returning home, Jasmine found she ___ her own umbrella in the classroom.","a":"left","b":"would leave","c":"had left","d":"have left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (found).","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm afraid I can't gather all the mangoes within such a short time ___ to help me tomorrow morning.","a":"unless you come","b":"unless you will come","c":"until you are coming","d":"until you will come","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to say that something will happen or be true if something else does not happen or is not true \n- Simple present tense (same tense with verb \"gather\") ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}